business-opportunities.biz 2019-01-28

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy describes how Business-Opportunities.biz owned and operated by Dig Deep Investments, LLC collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: Business-Opportunities.biz. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

Business-Opportunities.biz has been awarded TRUSTe’s Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with TRUSTe’s program requirements including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through these websites Business-Opportunities.biz. TRUSTe’s mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at info@ Business-Opportunities.biz.

* * *

NOTE: Business-Opportunities.biz is a partner of Google and Google Adsense and therefore data is collected on the pages of this website. For more information on [how Google uses data click here. ](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)

* * *

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

We also collect the following information from you

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system and store it in log files. We use this information to

  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Send you a catalog
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Display content based upon your interests

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality.

### Choice/Opt-Out

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz

### Information Obtained from Third Parties

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

### Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Business-Opportunities.biz is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We share your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz.

### Tracking Technologies

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Business-Opportunities.biz and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for our cart, to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference), for authentication. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

We and third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5 LSOs.

Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use LSOs such as Flash to collect and store information. To manage Flash LSOs please click here: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here. Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Business-Opportunities.biz. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz

### Additional Policy Information

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz.

 **Data Retention:** We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@Business-Opportunities.biz. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Updating Your Personal Information

Please note that users can not update or delete previously submitted information. If your information (such as your email address) should change, we ask that you re-submit a registration form or request.

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

 **Business-Opportunities.biz**  
1627 W. Main #298  
Bozeman, MT 59715  
Email: laurie@BusinessOpportunities.biz  
Phone: (406)581-2015
